(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T02:21:46.744421",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey! Every time I'm so proud of you
Ah Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと近づいてほ・し・い
I want you to come closer to me.
どんなことも
Whatever it is,
話してほしいのよ
I want you to talk to me about it!
Ah Touch my heart! & touch me please!
出来そうもないくらいな・こ・と
Even if it seems almost impossible,
おねだりしてくれていいよ
it's okay to ask me for it.
ずっと憧れてた人と
With the person I've always admired,
再会した
I've finally reunited.
運命感じなきゃ
If you don't feel it's destiny,
ウソだよ
you're in denial!
Now! Touch my heart!
100年経って地球が変わっても
Even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes,
気持ちは変わらないわ
my feelings will never change,
愛の園
here in this garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart!
1年...
Even if a year...
...なって 私が邪魔ならば
...and I'm in your way,
良い子の私は bye bye
it's bye-bye to the good girl in me.
Hey! Everytime I'm so proud of you
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart & Touch me please!
もっと意地悪でいいよ
You can be even meaner to me, it's fine.
過去も未来も あなたの自由でしょう
Both the past and future are up to you, right?
Touch my heart & Touch me please!
夢は夢と言うの？
Do you say dreams are just dreams?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know your dreams.
ずっと忘れない夜が続いているわ
These unforgettable nights keep going on.
運命抱きしめて 眠るわ
I'll fall asleep embracing destiny.
Now, touch my heart!
千年経って 宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, in this garden of love.
Now, touch my heart!
明日になって 私が邪魔ならば
When tomorrow comes, if I'm in your way,
良い子の私は bye bye
it's bye-bye to the good girl in me.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Let's go! 1, 2, 1, 2, 1!
Let's go! One, two, one, two, one!
Now, touch my heart!
千年経って 宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, in this garden of love.
Now, touch my heart!
明日になって 私が邪魔ならば
When tomorrow comes, if I'm in your way,
良い子の私は bye bye
it's bye-bye to the good girl in me.
Ah, bye bye
Ah, bye-bye.
Hey! Everytime I'm so proud of you
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Kikiriki~! Hi!
I am Takanashi Kiara from hololive English -Myth-!
And welcome to my birthday 3D live today!
The first song was an iconic, relatively old song
from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono"!
Yay! Did you like it?
There was like some funny moves, it's just like, "What am I?"
Yeah! So, um, as you can see,
today once again, I'm doing a Hello! Project cover song birthday festival!
Um, it's my second time to do like a Hello! Project cover song themed live.
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did!
And back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I still wanna do so badly!"
And that's why we're here today.
And yeah, so lots of Hello! Project songs to look forward to!
Also, ta-da! #KiaraBday2026,
please use it! Make me famous!
Take some screenshots, some clips, tell the internet about this, what's happening here!
Um, also let's talk a little bit about the background. What is this, you might wonder?
If you have watched a lot of Hello! Project music videos in your life,
you might actually recognize this, because it's from a Morning Musume song, like inspired from the music video.
Um, maybe an upcoming song, maybe after this!
So, we will have corners today. We are starting right now with the Morning Musume corner,
and then we'll have other corners too, that are all dedicated to my favorite Hello! Project groups.
And for each corner, there will be like a representative backdrop, like this one!
So, please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today. Mhm!
And now I'm kind of sad 'cause I danced alone, and I want some friends to come and help me perform.
So, shall we begin and continue with the next song?
Yes, yes! Bring in the ladies!
Come on!
泣いちゃうかも
[Naichau Kamo]
笑った顔をして返事した
You answered me with a smile on your face,
あなたが嘘をつく合図だね
that's your sign that you're lying to me.
二年目の記念を前にして
Right before our second anniversary,
私が振られちゃって終わるのね
it's all ending with you dumping me.
「また 一人ぼっち マリコ」
"All alone again, Mariko,"
自分に言い聞かす私
I tell myself.
気づかないフリをしていつまでも
Maybe I'll pretend not to notice forever
抱きしめられていようかな
and just stay held in your arms.
ああ あなたが優しいの分かってる
Ah, I know you're just being kind,
けど その分つらすぎるの
but that only makes it hurt all the more.
お祈りをしたけれど
Even though I said a prayer,
心は遠く離れてく
our hearts keep drifting further apart.
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Ah, I thought I'd say goodbye first,
そう思ったけど出来ない
but I just can't bring myself to.
会話の中で何度も
Countless times during our conversation,
タイミング見てたけど
I watched for the right moment, but...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも かも かも
I might, I might, I might!
どうしてそんな風に無理するの
Why do you push yourself like that?
嫌ならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't want this, just tell me goodbye.
わざとわがままをしてみたけど
I tried acting selfish on purpose,
優しく笑顔で答える人
but you're someone who just responds with a smile.
「もう これでいいの？ マリコ」
"Are you really okay with this, Mariko?"
自問自答をする私
I ask myself over and over.
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Hold me before you say it's the end.
ねえ 冷たくていいから
Hey, even if you're cold to me, it's fine.
その あなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is such a sin.
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
See, my resolve is already wavering.
出逢った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want to reassure each other every day.
ああ もう少しこのままでいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
When the final night arrives,
強気なフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも かも かも
I might, I might, I might!
その あなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is such a sin.
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
See, my resolve is already wavering.
ねぇ 出逢った頃みたいに
Hey, just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want to reassure each other every day.
ああ もう少しこのままでいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
When the final night arrives,
強気なフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも かも かも
I might, I might, I might!
早く 会いたいの…
"I want to see you soon..."
ねえ 早く あなたに会いたい…
"Hey, I want to see you soon..."
ヘイヤー ホエオエ
Hey-ya hoe-oe
Hey ya, ho-e-o-e
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh-e
Hey ya, ho-e-o
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh
先に向かってる ROAD
On the road heading forward
止まらない ミュージック
The music that never stops
恋人からの花束
A bouquet of flowers from my lover
真夜中届くメール
A message arriving in the dead of night
女の子なら
If you're a girl,
誰でも思う
everyone dreams of it
HAPPY END STORY
やさしくされりゃ
Being treated kindly
嬉しいけど
makes me happy, but
限りなく求めちゃう
I end up seeking endlessly more
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid,
じれったい キスもっと
I'm impatient for more kisses
熱い鼓動の
With a passionate heartbeat,
SEXY ISLAND
on this sexy island
笑ってる星も
The smiling stars and
気取ってる午後も
the pretentious afternoon,
この愛を見届けて
please watch over this love
ほしい
I want you to
Hey ya, ho-e-o-e
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh-e
Hey ya, ho-e-o
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh
海が輝いて ジェラシー
The shining ocean makes me jealous
独り言の週末
A weekend of talking to myself
あなたといたなら 嬉しい
I'd be so happy if I were with you
不思議な匂い スイーティ
A mysterious scent, sweetie
寂しい夜と
Lonely nights and
楽しい時間
fun times
HAPPY END STORY
もう一度言うわ
I'll say it once more:
大好きです
I love you so much
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me tight and don't let go
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit,
じれったい ミスショット
an agonizing missed shot
ずっと続くの
Will it continue forever
SEXY ISLAND
on this sexy island?
愛して急接近
Love and rapidly draw close
未来に大接近
Approaching the future fast
どこまでも抱きしめて
Hold me tightly wherever we go
ほしい
I want you to
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid,
じれったい キスもっと
I'm impatient for more kisses
熱い鼓動の
With a passionate heartbeat,
SEXY ISLAND
on this sexy island
笑ってる星も
The smiling stars and
気取ってる午後も
the pretentious afternoon,
この愛を見届けて
please watch over this love
ほしい
I want you to
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit,
じれったい ミスショット
an agonizing missed shot
ずっと続くの
Will it continue forever
SEXY ISLAND
on this sexy island?
愛して急接近
Love and rapidly draw close
未来に大接近
Approaching the future fast
どこまでも抱きしめて
Hold me tightly wherever we go
ほしい
I want you to
Hey ya, ho-e-o-e
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh-e
Hey ya, ho-e-o
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh
Hey ya, ho-e-o-e
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh-e
Hey ya, ho-e-o
Hey-ya, ho-e-oh
渋谷を歩く
Walking through Shibuya
一人で歩く
Walking all alone
人ごみの中
In the middle of the crowd
「大好き」なあの人探す
Looking for the one I love so much
手を繋いでいい？ その思いから
"Can I hold your hand?" Ever since that thought,
歌とはぐれて 見てただけの夜
I got lost from the song, just watching the night
「あの人を...」
"That person..."
「こんな私を...」
"Someone like me..."
どうか離さないで ねぇ
Please don't let me go, okay?
恋する想いが My Darling
These feelings in love, My Darling,
大きく膨らみ I love you
swell so large, I love you
考えすぎたら My Darling
If I overthink it, My Darling,
空回りしたわ
I end up spinning my wheels
まだまだ私は My Darling
I'm still, My Darling,
あなたが怖いわ I love you
scared of you, I love you
きっといつの日か My Darling
Surely someday, My Darling,
嫌われちゃいそうで
I feel like you'll come to hate me
Ah
あなたを見つめ 涙が出ちゃった
Staring at you, tears began to fall
少し前から 私に気づいてたらなんて
Wondering, "What if you had noticed me a while back?"
少しずるいよ だけど言えない
That's a bit unfair, but I can't say it
最初のきっかけは 私だし
Since I was the one who started it all
そうよ うつむいてたら 手を握ってくれたわ
That's right, when I looked down, you held my hand
おとなになっても My Darling
Even when we become adults, My Darling,
もっとその先も I love you
and far beyond that too, I love you
腰が曲がっても My Darling
Even when our backs are bent with age, My Darling,
手をつなぐ時には
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう My Darling
our hearts will flutter, won't they? My Darling
恥ずかしいでしょう I love you
It'll be embarrassing, won't it? I love you
それでも私を My Darling
Even so, My Darling,
優しく包んでね
gently embrace me
Ah
おとなになっても My Darling
Even when we become adults, My Darling,
もっとその先も I love you
and far beyond that too, I love you
腰が曲がっても My Darling
Even when our backs are bent with age, My Darling,
手をつなぐ時には
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう My Darling
our hearts will flutter, won't they? My Darling
恥ずかしいでしょう I love you
It'll be embarrassing, won't it? I love you
それでも私を My Darling
Even so, My Darling,
優しく包んでね
gently embrace me
Ah
涙の色
[Song: Color of Tears]
強情 あなたは強情
Stubborn, you're so stubborn
わからず屋のままね
Still as senseless as ever
もう付き合いきれない
I can't deal with you anymore
サヨナラ 愛し人
Goodbye, my beloved
友情
Friendship
「友達」なんて 戻れるわけないでしょ
There's no way we could go back to being "friends"
この先もわがままに
Do you plan to keep selfishly
振り回すつもり？
jerking me around from now on too?
浮気なら それなりに
If it was just cheating, in my own way,
許すつもりだった
I intended to forgive you
プライドを傷つけた
You wounded my pride,
あの日は許せない
and that day I cannot forgive
涙 止まらぬ涙
Tears, these unceasing tears
これでスッキリするわ
This will leave me refreshed
あなたを信じてた
Having believed in you—
あの日がもったいない
that day was such a waste
Ah Ah
それでも愛してた
Even so, I loved you...
あなたとのサヨナラ
It's goodbye to you.
動揺
Trembling,
心の隙間
an opening in my heart...
風邪を引きそうだけど
It feels like I might catch a cold,
それならすぐ治るし
but if it's just that, I'll get better soon...
サヨナラ 愛し人
Goodbye, my beloved.
薄情
Heartless,
どう言われても
no matter what you call me,
縒りを戻さないから
because I won't get back together with you.
もう電話は出ないわ
I won't answer your calls anymore,
どんなに寂しくても
no matter how lonely I feel.
いつもより早いけど
Even though it's earlier than usual,
ベッドに入るわ
I'm going to get into bed.
懐かしい記憶との
It's time to do battle
戦いの時間 Ah
with fond memories, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears...
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私も強情ね
I guess I'm stubborn too;
今頃そう思うわ
that's what I think now.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ Ah
but it's goodbye to you, ah...
涙 止まらぬ 涙
Tears, unstoppable tears...
これでスキッとするわ
This will help clear my head.
あなたを信じてた
The time I spent believing in you—
あの日がもったいない Ah
that day was such a waste, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears...
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私も強情ね
I guess I'm stubborn too;
今頃そう思うわ
that's what I think now.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ Ah
but it's goodbye to you, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
but it's goodbye to you.
イェーイ！
Yay!
やったー！イェーイ！Welcome, welcome!
Yay! Woohoo! Welcome, welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
That was FOREVER LOVE and 涙の色 with FLOW GLOW!
That was "FOREVER LOVE" and "Namida no Iro" with FLOW GLOW!
イェーイ！踊ってもらいました！
Yay! Thanks for dancing with us!
It's like I'm a member of FLOW GLOW!
イエス！6人目のメンバー！ありがとうございます！
Yes! The 6th member! Thank you so much!
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいです！こんなに大人数で踊れて。
Seriously, I'm so happy to dance with such a big group!
まずは自己紹介をみんなに、英語でやってもらおうかな？
First off, why don't you all do your self-introductions in English?
ええー！？英語！？
Eeh?! In English?!
ヤバい！できるかな？インターナショナル...
Oh no! Can we do it? International...
順番はお任せしますけど。
I'll leave the order up to you guys.
おっ、じゃあいつもの順番で！
Oh, let's go in our usual order then!
オッケー！英語で頑張れ！
Okay! Do your best in English!
Hello, everyone! My name is Riona!
I'm FLOW GLOW leader, blah blah... Yeah! Nice to meet you!
完璧！イェーイ！次は？
Perfect! Yay! Who's next?
あー！
Ah!
にこちゃん、come here! Come here! Yeah!
Niko-chan, come here! Come here! Yeah!
My name is Koganei Niko! FLOW GLOW's uh comedy modoki, yeah!
My name is Koganei Niko! FLOW GLOW's, uh, comedy wannabe, yeah!
モドキ！？イェーイ！
Wannabe?! Yay!
英語がちょっと足りないけどw
A bit lacking in English, though, haha.
はい！シュピシュワー！Big car, rhythm ya sou, yeah!
Hi! Supishuwa! Big... car? Rhythm, ya so, yeah!
あれ？PR担当！Please, please... ah!
Wait, what? PR rep! Please, please... ah!
PR担当！
In charge of PR!
すぅちゃん、日本語の「大きい」は英語で「small」...
Su-chan, the Japanese for "big" is "small" in English...
No! 違う違う！Big! Yes!
No! No, no! Big! Yes!
Trust me, thank you! バカだと思っているな、キアラ先輩！
Trust me, thank you! You think I'm stupid, Kiara-senpai!
さすがに分かったかw はい、次！
You caught that after all, lol. Alright, next!
Hi! FLOW GLOW's DJ and driver, Rindo Chihaya!
伸ばしてギャル鉄砲ー！
Extend and Gyaru Gun!
おっとっと / うー！
Whoa, whoa! / Ooh!
Wow, Big taki...?
Big suki? Big beef?
はい！せーの！
Okay! Ready, set...
うー、VIVI！
Ooh, Vivi!
うー、I'm すげえよ、キキララビビって！
Ooh, I'm amazing, Kiki-rara, be scared!
Ah, yeah!
すげえよがそんな共通認識じゃないかもしれない...
"Sugeeyo" might not be common knowledge...
Well, uh, when I chose to do these songs, I really wanted to bring in ReGLOSS because I know they're all really good at dancing, yeah,
and performing. みんなパフォーマンスうまいから、絶対ReGLOSSを誘おうと思って、完成度高いと思って。
and performing. Everyone is so good at performing, so I definitely wanted to invite ReGLOSS, thinking it'd be high quality.
嬉しい！
We're so happy!
でも、あの、なんか困ったこととか、難しかった振りとか何かありましたか？
But, um, were there any troubles or difficult choreography?
全部！全部難しかった！
Everything! Everything was difficult!
え、でもかっこよかった！みんなの、なんか揃ったの見た時にめっちゃかっこいいってなりました。
Eh, but it looked so cool! When I saw everyone synchronized, I was like, "That's so cool!"
私も！なんかその、みんなでどんどん出来上がって、
Me too! As we gradually built it up together...
完成度が高くなっていくうちに...
and the quality got higher and higher...
もう幸せすぎて！ / イエーイ！
I was just so happy! / Yay!
みんな「かっこいい」って言ってくれてて嬉しかった！ / みんなかっこよかった！
I was so glad everyone said we looked cool! / Everyone looked so cool!
なんかカノンで結構交互の振りみたいな... / こういうのね
Like doing canon-style alternating choreography... / Like this, right?
のが今まであんまりなかったから、そう、キアラ先輩にね、呼んでもらってそれができて嬉しかったです！
...we hadn't really done that before, so I was really happy Kiara-senpai invited us and we got to do it!
嬉しかったー！
We were so happy!
そうだね、なんか、あの、順番で回るとか... 結構多くて...
Yeah, like taking turns spinning around... there was a lot of that...
ねー、大変でした。
Yeah, it was tough.
まあ、すいません、難しい振り付け。あの、皆さんのコーナーは、℃-uteのコーナーであって...
Well, sorry for the difficult choreography. Um, your section was the ℃-ute section...
お！やったー！
Oh! Yay!
℃-uteっていうグループは、ダンスがマジでいつも難しいです。 / 確かにねー！実力派！
The group ℃-ute's dances are seriously always difficult. / Totally! They're so skilled!
ごめんね、でもみんなよくできた！ / めっちゃ楽しかった！ありがとうございます！
Sorry about that, but everyone did great! / It was so fun! Thank you so much!
℃-uteと言えば、I want to know everybody's like favorite Hello! Project song!
Speaking of ℃-ute, I want to know everybody's favorite Hello! Project song!
あの、ハロプロで好きな曲、曲、知りたいけど...
Um, I'd love to know your favorite Hello! Project song...
じゃ、まず... ありますか？ / あ、アモーレ！アモーレ！
So, first... do you have one? / Ah, Amore! Amore!
アモーレ！ / あれが好き！
Amore! / I love that one!
おお、いいね、最近の曲ですね、いいですね。あと、あーくんは？
Oh, nice, that's a recent song, isn't it? That's great. And what about Ao-kun?
あーくん...「バカ野郎、あんた！女自分転がして生きてやる！」
Ao-kun... "You idiot! I'll live rolling with being a woman!"
あれが好きです！大好き！
I love that one! Love it!
いいよねー！ / あーくんらしい！
That's so good! / So like Ao-kun!
わかる！結構オタクと聞いて... / そうですね、えっと...
I know! I heard she's quite an otaku... / That's right, well...
そう、私の好きな曲はモーニング娘。'14さんの『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』
Yeah, my favorite song is Morning Musume '14's "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe"!
あー！好き！やばい！ / 本当に名曲で！
Ah! I love that! Amazing! / It's truly a masterpiece!
『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』ってすごいかっこいい！ / かっこいい！しっとり系！
"Toki wo koe sora wo koe" is so cool! / So cool! A mellow vibe!
でもお前、スマイレージは『ぁまのじゃく』そうだけど...
Wait, for S/mileage, "Amanojaku" seemed to be...
『ぁまのじゃく』は、クロちゃん去年やってたんですよ！ / そう、『ぁまのじゃく』大好きです！
Chloe performed "Amanojaku" last year! / Yeah, I love "Amanojaku"!
なるほど！詳しいそうですね。オタクだねー！
I see! You seem so knowledgeable. Total otaku!
で、ラデちゃんはどの曲が好き？ / 私はあの、『ホントのじぶん』
And Rade-chan, which song do you like? / For me, it's "Honto no Jibun".
『ホントのじぶん』ねー、があの、初めて聴いた時にめっちゃ素敵な曲だなと思って、大好き！
"Honto no Jibun"... when I first heard it, I thought it was such a wonderful song, I love it!
Buono!ですね！Buono!、みんな大好きなBuono!ですが。 / Buono!さん大好き！ / わかる！
Buono!, right! Everyone loves Buono!. / I love Buono!. / I know, right!
で、ビビは？ / はい！ビビは、『チュッ！ 夏パ〜ティ』！
And Bibi? / Yes! Bibi likes "Chu! Natsu Party"!
キアラ先輩にチューしたいわ！
I wanna kiss Kiara-senpai!
チュチュチュチュ... やめてー！
Chu chu chu chu... Stop it!
キアラ先輩騙されないでください！
Kiara-senpai, don't let her trick you!
なんでだよ！騙すってなんだよ！
Why?! What do you mean "trick"?!
かわいい！でも、このいろんな曲名を聞くだけで、このハロプロカバーソングライブ、何度でも何度でもやりたいですけど...
So cute! But just hearing all these song titles makes me want to do this Hello! Project cover live again and again...
やりたい！
We want to!
とりあえずは、あの、まだまだあります！℃-uteの次に他のパートも、他のグループもありますので、
For now, there's still plenty more! After ℃-ute, we have other parts and other groups too,
え、次のパートに行きましょう！ReGLOSSのみんなありがとペン！ / ありがとうございましたー！
so let's move on to the next part! Thanks to everyone in ReGLOSS-pen! / Thank you so much!
ということで、Let's go to the next corner!
With that said, let's go to the next corner!
レッツ... ゴー！
Let's... go!
S/mileage
[Title: S/mileage]
Inugami Korone
[Title: Inugami Korone]
Usada Pekora
[Title: Usada Pekora]
Watson Amelia
[Title: Watson Amelia]
S/mileage
[Title: S/mileage]
Wah-hoo!
Wah, wah, wah, wah-hoo!
いまだかつてないような
Like nothing I've ever experienced before,
キラキラした毎日
every single day is sparkling!
ぶっちゃけ有頂天な日々送ってる
Frankly, I'm spending my days on cloud nine!
Wah, wah, wah, wah-hoo!
恋をしたら勉強が
Ever since I fell in love,
手につかない毎日
I can't focus on my studies every day.
恋のせいにしちゃって…ないっ！
Am I blaming it on love...? No way!
今日はデート
Today's a date,
彼と10時に待ち合わせてるの
I'm meeting him at 10:00!
Wow wow
今日 香りを少し
Today, I changed my perfume a little...
変えた事 気付くかしら 君は
Will you notice it, I wonder?
Wow wow
ドクターストップがかかるほど
So deeply that a doctor would tell me to stop,
「恋落ち」してるわ
I'm falling head over heels!
大好きが止まらない
I just can't stop loving you!
Oh love me love me love me love me love me do !
Oh love me love me love me love me love me do!
Wah, wah, wah, wah-hoo!
カルチャーショックを起こすほど
Big enough to cause a culture shock,
時代を変えるわ
we're gonna change the era!
Wah-hoo!
スポットライトを浴びる二人
The two of us bathed in the spotlight...
口づけをしましょう
Let's share a kiss!
I love you !
I love you!
Wah-hoo!
女の子には秘密の
Girls have a secret...
恋のボタンがあるのよ
love button, you know?
今年の夏は負けない
I won't lose this summer!
去年みたいに弱くない
I won't be weak like last year!
Ah that's summer love 胸が騒ぐわ
Ah, that's summer love! My heart is racing!
That's summer love
実際恋するだけなら誰でも出来る
Honestly, anyone can just fall in love.
勇気を持って輝こう
Let's find courage and shine!
実際恋愛するのってタイミング
In truth, real romance is all about timing,
見逃せない
I can't let it pass me by!
夏祭り 手を繋ぎ
At the summer festival, holding hands,
花火を見上げて
looking up at the fireworks...
きれいだと 私見て
"So pretty," you look at me
君が言う
and say...
浴衣着て 金魚すくい
In our yukatas, scooping goldfish,
君が3匹で
you catch three of them...
…なんて恋
...That kind of romance,
夢見てる 15歳
dreaming of it at fifteen!
ひとりきり イヤフォンで
All by myself, with earphones in,
音楽聴いている
listening to music...
意味もなく 涙とか
For no reason at all, tears
出てきちゃう
start spilling over...
wow oh さみしいよ さみしいよ
Wow oh, I feel so lonely, so lonely...
なぜかさみしいよ
For some reason, I feel so lonely...
すごい恋
An amazing love,
夢見てる 15歳
dreaming of it at fifteen!
summer love !
Summer love!
ついて来る気があるんでしょうか
Do you really intend to follow me?
ねぇ君は
Hey, do you?
オドオドしてちゃ
If you hesitate like that,
飲み込まれるよ 都会では
you'll be swallowed up by the city.
愛だ恋だと言うつもりなら
If you're going to talk about love and romance,
それなりに
then do it right—
男らしくて 自信ありげで
manfully, with confidence,
さわやかに
and refreshing charm.
私だってそりゃね 甘えたいと思う
Of course, I want to be spoiled too,
だけど甘い顔は 出来ない立場なの
but my position doesn't let me show a soft side.
胸元のあいた服を着た私の
Notice the signals from me
サインに気づいて ねぇ
in this low-cut dress, hey...
愛してよ
Love me!
誰にも負けず 愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて！
Love me more than anyone, love me, love me to pieces!
安心感 優越感 それが欲しいの
A sense of security, of superiority—that's what I want.
抱きしめて
Hold me tight,
生まれたまんまの裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a bare, bare, naked kiss just like how we were born.
この愛が本物とわかればいいの
As long as I know this love is real, that's enough.
この愛が本物とわかるように KISSして
Kiss me so that I know this love is real.
愛してよ
Love me!
燃え尽きる程 愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて！
Love me until we burn out, love me, love me to pieces!
少し位 強引で丁度いいのよ
Being a little forceful is just right.
抱きしめて
Hold me tight,
生まれたまんまの裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a bare, bare, naked kiss just like how we were born.
この愛が本物とわかればいいの
As long as I know this love is real, that's enough.
この愛が本物とわかるように KISSして
Kiss me so that I know this love is real.
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ (盛れ！)
Glam up, mi amore! (Glam up!)
盛れ！ (盛れ！) 盛れ！ (盛れ！)
Glam up! (Glam up!) Glam up! (Glam up!)
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore,
一番の私を見て
look at the very best version of me.
ありのままなんて 愛したくない
I don't want to love what's merely "as is."
火花みたいな 今を
In this moment, dazzling like sparks!
盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up, glam up, glam up!
あなたの瞳はフィルター
Your eyes are like a filter,
燃えてゆく恋は刹那
a burning romance in an instant.
思い出なら 綺麗なまま
If it becomes a memory, keep it beautiful—
笑っていられないの
I can't just stand here smiling.
泣いて変なメイクも 一瞬素顔になれば
Even if my makeup runs from tears, if I show my bare face for a moment,
即 修正だけど あなたにこそ踏み拓け
it'll be fixed instantly, but step right in for you!
こだわりの角度で 悪魔でも味方につける
At my ideal angle, I'll even get the devil on my side.
美しさの毒を ずっと焼き付けて
Burn the poison of my beauty deep into your heart.
油断できないわ シャッターチャンス
I can't let my guard down—it's a shutter chance!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore,
私を好きでいさせて
let me keep being in love with you.
ありのままなんて 慰めたくない
I don't want consolation saying "just as you are."
現実以上でいいの
Being better than reality is just fine!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore,
一番の私を見て
look at the very best version of me.
ありのままなんて 愛したくない
I don't want to love what's merely "as is."
火花みたいな 今を
In this moment, dazzling like sparks!
盛れ！
Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore,
あなたを好きでいさせて
let me keep loving you.
愛してよかったと 思うはずだわ
You'll surely be glad you loved me,
綺麗じゃないわ だけど
though it's not all pretty, but still...
盛れ！ ミ・アモーレ
Glam up, mi amore!
私の元を去る日も
Even on the day you leave my side,
悲しみよりもね 跡が残る
more than sadness, leave a lasting trace.
めちゃくちゃにして離そう
Mess me up completely before letting go!
盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up, glam up, glam up!
ライ ライ ライ ライ ララライ ララライ
Lai lai lai lai la la lai la la lai
ライライ ライララライララ
Lai, lai, lai, la-la-lai-la-la
M-O-R-E M-O-R-E Ah...
オーレ！
Olé!
Go! Go!
Do it! Do it!
Ah!
今夜は会えそうにないやいやい
Seems like we won't be able to meet tonight, yeah, yeah
不思議と寂しいやいやいやいやい
It feels strangely lonely, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
背伸びをしてるわけじゃないのに
Even though I'm not trying to act all grown-up...
胸が痛い
...my chest hurts so much.
仲間が集まって ガキ扱い
All our friends gather and treat me like a kid,
今すぐ 大人になりたいやい
I want to become an adult right now, yeah.
こんなに苦しいのが
Is being in this much pain...
初恋ですか？
...what first love really is?
アーケード 走り抜け
Running through the arcade,
信号が青になる
the traffic light turns green.
あの人が
That special someone,
この時間
at this exact time,
ここを通る
passes right by here.
ほら 春紅のスカーレット
Look, it's the spring-red scarlet!
我慢なんて出来ない
There's no way I can hold back!
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet flutter in my heart,
恋の色が香る
the fragrance of the color of love.
yes, my love
Do it! Do it!
Ah!
Yeah!
Ah 週末は みんなワイワイワイ
Ah, on weekends everyone is having fun,
なぜなの あなたいないやいやい
so why aren't you here, yeah, yeah?
こんな日は つまらない
Days like this are so boring,
そろそろ帰ろうかな
I think I'll head back home soon.
噂じゃ 彼女が出来たとか
Rumor has it you got a girlfriend,
そんなのまったく聞きたくない
but I don't want to hear about that at all!
張り裂けそうな くらい
It feels like it's going to burst...
頭が斜め
...my head is spinning!
雨が降る 週末は
On weekends when it rains,
少し街も静か
the town gets a little quiet too.
このままじゃ 眠れない
At this rate, I won't be able to sleep,
切なすぎる
it's just too painful.
ああ 春紅のスカーレット
Ah, the spring-red scarlet!
そっと近づきたい
I want to gently draw closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet flutter in my heart,
恋の虹が光る
the rainbow of love shines bright.
yes, my love
Woo!
ほら 春紅のスカーレット
Look, it's the spring-red scarlet!
我慢なんて出来ない
There's no way I can hold back!
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet flutter in my heart,
恋の色が香る
the fragrance of the color of love.
yes, my love
春紅のスカーレット
The spring-red scarlet,
そっと近づきたい
I want to gently draw closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet flutter in my heart,
恋の虹が光る
the rainbow of love shines bright.
yes, my love
Do it! Do it!
Yay! Woo!
Here we go! Woohoo!
Oh my god!
Welcome, Bae!
Yay! Hi!
Kiwa, happy birthday!
Oh, thank you!
It's—it's not just my birthday,
but it's another celebration because this is the first time that we're together as just two...
...dancing!
Yay!
What—what an occasion!
How have we come to this occasion? You will never know, but please introduce yourself.
Oh, what's up? I am Chaos, the End of Ends,
a steward trapped in a cage of ice, your best friend, Hakos Baelz from hololive English -Promise-! Witness...
...me!
Smooth introduction.
Whoa, I wish I had such an introduction!
Well, welcome, welcome, welcome! How did you like the song?
It was so hard! Yeah, really hard.
I don't do idol dances. This—this is so hard.
Ah, this, yeah, it happens often in Hello! Project, but...
I don't understand!
Well, this... I remember in the dance lesson, you told me about the different genres of dance that appeared in this dance.
Yeah, I was quite surprised. There was a lot of house. This is quite house-y.
This is house?
House.
Okay.
And then there was also, there was locking.
Ah, this? You said that's rock?
This is locking.
L-Locking?
Oh, you meant locking, not rocking?
No, locking.
Ah! I thought that was a rock dance style, okay.
Misunderstanding.
Yeah! That was so hard!
Good job. I was so surprised! I was like, what kind of idol dance has house and locking in the same dance? That's crazy.
They were trying all kinds of things back then, but, yeah, that's from my favorite idol group, Berryz Kobo.
And it's like a pretty old song at this point, but it has this one part in the choreography that I thought would be perfect for like a duo.
So I thought, I wanna do it with you together!
Yay! It's this part.
Da, da, da...
It was so much fun!
I really wanted to do it, thank you!
Yay!
Okay, um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
A game?
A game of cameras!
There's so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera.
Uh...
Is this the first camera that we're looking for, so far? Maybe it's like here?
Uh, uh, yeah.
Camera! Yay!
ヤッホ～！
Yaho~!
I see, I see, I see. Yeah!
Okay, Bae, you find the next one. Where is that?
Is it there, or is it the opposite?
I will find it first!
Where is it? Where is it?
あれ？ あれ？ あれ？ あれ？
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Well, if we continue running around, surely we will find it eventually.
Wait, hold on.
Right there!
Wait, wait, wait, no. I see it, right there!
Hi! Hello!
Hi!
That was really difficult.
That was fun. Next camera!
Where is it?
Where did they find these cameras?
I see it!
When has this angle ever been used?
I know!
Hi~
こんにちは～
Hello~
Woo~
One more, one more, one more, one more!
One more!
Under a disco ball?
Wait, I saw the shadow.
Wait, the disco ball should be like...
No!
No, it's like...
No.
It's not there.
It's like...
Ah, it's hard to...
Am I looking at it?
Ah! Yeah! Yeah!
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, one, one ラスト？ ラスト？ Last one.
Wait, one, one last one? Last one? Last one.
Is that the last one? Well, well, this one's easy because...
That's not a challenge!
Hi!
Yay!
Yeah!
Okay, okay, okay! That was fun!
Well, well, well. Well...
Yes, this is not the end, though!
No, no, no, not at all.
What are you doing next?
Well, first of all, the Berryz Kobo corner will continue for one more song, because I love them so much.
Oh!
And for the next one, I have four guests!
Four?!
And they are none other than Justice!
Because last year, for the Easter Hello! Project cover song live, I also had them over, but they were like in 2D, like in a paper form.
Oh!
So I thought, well this year I get them all in 3D!
3D Justice!
Yeah! And they will be wearing like a little bit of a costume?
A cosplay? Oh, a cosplay!
Something like that. Costume, cosplay...
...that matches the music video.
Oh my.
So pay attention to what's different.
And with that, I guess, have fun with the rest of the show!
And the next song, which is...
せ～の！
Ready, set...
青春バスガイド！
Seishun Bus Guide!
Woo!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today we say goodbye, my heart aches
手紙書いていいんだろう？
It's okay if I write you a letter, right?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth bus guide, you're dazzling
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a photo with you as a keepsake?
一目惚れなんだ
It was love at first sight
僕がはじけた
I burst with excitement
とまらない感覚
This unstoppable sensation—
これが恋だろう
this must be love
君とすれ違う
When I passed by you,
いいにおいした
you smelled so nice
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be so nice to everyone!
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, everything
目線が合う度しびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I get chills
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
But we must say goodbye, my heart aches
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth bus guide, you're dazzling
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I wish I could be reborn as your microphone
あいつもライバル
That guy is a rival too,
話しかけてる
he's talking to you
沸き起こる感覚
This feeling welling up inside—
これがジェラシー
this must be jealousy
休憩時間に
During our break,
少し会話できた
I got to talk with you for a bit
まつげがとても長いね
Your eyelashes are so long
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back
最初の日にもどりたい
I want to go back to the first day
君に伝えたいことばかり
There are so many things I want to tell you
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, everything
目線が合う度しびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I get chills
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today we say goodbye, my heart aches
手紙書いていいんだろう？
It's okay if I write you a letter, right?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth bus guide, you're dazzling
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a photo with you as a keepsake?
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
But we must say goodbye, my heart aches
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth bus guide, you're dazzling
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once again
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
[Special Generation]
どうたら こうたら 言い訳してる
Making excuses about this and that
イライラくるなぁ
It's so irritating!
あの子が良いなら
If you like that girl better,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
why don't you just go with her?
チャラチャラ チャラチャラ シルバー着けて
Flashing and jangling around wearing silver jewelry,
フラフラしてる
wandering aimlessly
誰にアピってるの？
Who are you trying to impress?
余所見なんて 許さないわよ
I won't let you look at anyone else!
好きと 好きと 好きと 好きと言いなさい
Say that you love me, love me, love me, love me!
そう この場で
Yes, right here, right now!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
運命を信じたい
I want to believe in destiny
100万年過ぎたって この愛は ゆるぎない
Even after a million years, this love won't waver
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
嫌いにもなれないわ
I could never hate you
地下鉄の中だって 過去よりも...
Even on the subway, more than in the past...
過去よりも
More than in the past,
あ・い・し・て
l-o-v-e m-e!
Ah!
Woah woah yeah
ジェネレーション！
Generation!
会ったら 会ったで
When we meet up,
どこに行くでも
no matter where we go,
ダラダラしてる
we just fool around.
私が決めなきゃ
If I don't decide,
なんも始まんない
nothing ever starts.
押したり 引いたり
Pushing and pulling,
なんて器用に
doing things so smoothly,
する事出来ない
I just can't do that.
まっすぐ行くだけよ
I can only go straight ahead!
誰も彼も 驚くような
So surprising that everyone would be amazed,
熱い愛で
with your passionate love,
私 私 抱きしめて
hold me, hold me tight!
Ah!
HOLD ON MY LOVE
スッペシャル ジェネレ～ション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は え・い・え・ん
this love is f-o-r-e-v-e-r!
スッペシャル ジェネレ～ション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
離れない 離さない
I won't leave, I won't let go!
昨日よりも 今よりも
More than yesterday, more than right now,
また明日も あ・い・し・て
tomorrow too, l-o-v-e m-e!
Ah!
Woah woah yeah
スッペシャル ジェネレ～ション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は え・い・え・ん
this love is f-o-r-e-v-e-r!
スッペシャル ジェネレ～ション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE
離れない 離さない
I won't leave, I won't let go!
昨日よりも 今よりも
More than yesterday, more than right now,
また明日も あ・い・し・て
tomorrow too, l-o-v-e m-e!
Woah woah yeah
ジェネレーション！
Generation!
スッ！
Su!
ペ！
Pe!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション！
Special Generation!
Thank you so much everybody!
Thank you for coming, thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!
よし！
Alright!
One more!
カモン！
Kapow!
Bye-bye!
Announcement, announcement!
Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
Here is the banner.
First of all, the big item that is the main character is a dakimakura!
I finally did it after so many years of doing merchandise.
I might be running out of ideas a little bit, so
I did something that originally I never thought I would do.
KFP, don't leave me hanging...
leave me laying on the bed, yeah!
1つ目のアイテムはなんと！ 一生やらないと思ってたんですけど、
The first item is, what do you know! I thought I'd never do it in my life, but...
やっぱりここまで活動すると、もう出すしかなかった、
as expected, after being active for so long, I had no choice but to release it:
抱き枕です！
It's a body pillow!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Next, we have a really cute plushie set of my kitty-cats,
Smoothie and Chonkers!
They're so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now, and you should too!
You can hang them on your bag or keys.
え、2つ目のアイテムは、そうですね、私の猫たちのぬいぐるみセットで、
Um, the second item is, that's right, a plushie set of my cats,
キーチェーンなどとして使えます！
and you can use them as keychains and such!
え、どこにでも連れてってあげてください！
Please take them along with you wherever you go!
Next one is these badges, but they are a bit unusual,
because this time they are square and made from fake leather,
so they're a bit squishy.
Of course you can make an ita-bag with this too!
今回のバッジはなんと、
The badges this time are, amazingly,
ええと、フェイクレザーでできてますし、あと四角だし、変わっておりますが、
made of fake leather, and they're square and unique, but
もちろんこれでも痛バとかできたりしますよ！
of course, you can make ita-bags with them too!
Last item is the smartphone ring, modeled after KFP chickens!
Maybe this way, holding your phones won't be as hard with your wings.
Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング！
The last item is a smartphone ring!
もちろんKFPモチーフです！
Naturally with a KFP motif!
Besides that, there's also a voice pack!
I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months, so make sure to get this one.
Rare!
そのほかには、久しぶりにボイスもあります！
Other than that, we have a voice pack for the first time in a while!
最近あんまり参加してないので、
I haven't done many of them lately,
ぜひこの機会にお願いします！
so please definitely take this chance to get it!
If you get the full set, then you receive a Polaroid from me alongside it,
and if you're lucky to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands.
もちろんいつも通りフルセットゲットすると、えー、ま、チェキついてきます！
Of course, as always, if you get the full set, you'll receive an instant photo card!
限定版だとキアラのサイン入りですね！
The limited edition comes with Kiara's handwritten signature!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Please check it out!
And one more thing before we end,
I have a super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
It's a collaboration with some cuties that might be familiar to you:
ISEGYE IDOL! Yay, ISEGYE IDOL!
この後は韓国のVTuberアイドル、ISEGYE IDOLとのコラボ、歌ってみたプレミア公開しますので、見てくださーい！
After this, my song cover collab with Korean VTuber idol group ISEGYE IDOL premieres, so please check it out!
I will try our best to raid you into it,
but if it does not work out, please make your way there on your own!
Besides that, thank you so much for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this, and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merchandise!
And in German, we say: Auf Wiedersehen!
最後に、今日はお誕生日お祝いに来てくれてありがとうございました！
Lastly, thank you so much for coming to celebrate my birthday today!
本当に色々努力してきたのです。
I've really put a lot of hard work into this.
コメントといいね、そしてもしよかったらグッズもよろしくお願いいたします！
Please leave a comment, a like, and if you'd like, check out the merch as well!
ではでは、Auf Wiedersehen!
Well then, Auf Wiedersehen!
See you in the song cover!